<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>sensei</title>
  
  <subtitle>Lightweight, zero-copy simulation adaptor.</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://kitware.github.io/sensei/"/>
  <updated>2018-05-09T20:41:02.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://kitware.github.io/sensei/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>sensei</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Supercomputing 2018 Tutorial</title>
    <link href="https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2018/05/07/20180507-tutorial-submitted/"/>
    <id>https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2018/05/07/20180507-tutorial-submitted/</id>
    <published>2018-05-07T12:41:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-05-09T20:41:02.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We’ve submitted a proposal to present a SENSEI tutorial at <a href="https://sc18.supercomputing.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Supercomputing 2018</a> and will hear back on June 8th whether or not it was accepted.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;We’ve submitted a proposal to present a SENSEI tutorial at &lt;a href=&quot;https://sc18.supercomputing.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Supe
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Website</title>
    <link href="https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2018/05/04/20180504-website/"/>
    <id>https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2018/05/04/20180504-website/</id>
    <published>2018-05-04T16:35:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-05-09T20:41:02.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In order to make the SENSEI website more dynamic, we will start using github pages to host the website.The website is generated from files in the <code>doc</code> directory of the sensei repository.</p><p>The process for updating the website is:</p><ul><li>Ensure you have installed <a href="https://nodejs.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">nodejs</a> and <a href="https://npmjs.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">npm</a> and run the one-time setup command:<code>npm install</code> from the <code>doc</code> directory of your sensei clone.This will create a <code>node_modules</code> directory inside <code>doc</code> containingjavascript libraries needed to generate and publish the website.You only need to do this once per clone of sensei.</li><li>Add new files to the <code>doc/content</code> directory as needed (more on this below).</li><li>Test the new website by running <code>npm run doc:www</code> and visit http://127.0.0.1:4000/in your web browser. Verify that the page you’ve added or edited appears properly.</li><li>Commit your changes to the master branch of sense by submitting a merge request.</li><li>Once the changes are in master, you should <em>publish</em> the changes to the <code>gh-pages</code>branch of the repository. For the moment, this is a manual process: run<code>npm run doc:publish</code> in the <code>doc</code> directory of your clone.</li></ul><h2 id="Adding-new-files"><a href="#Adding-new-files" class="headerlink" title="Adding new files"></a>Adding new files</h2><p>First of all, <strong>do not add large or binary files</strong> to the repository.If you want to include images, link to PDFs, etc. then upload themto the <a href="https://data.kitware.com/#collection/5a007cb58d777f31ac64ddfd" target="_blank" rel="noopener">sensei in situ collection</a> on https://data.kitware.com/and reference them by URL in the markdown files you add here.</p><p>There are several kinds of files you might wish to add to sensei:+ To add a blog post, simply add a new markdown file in <code>doc/content/_posts</code>.  If you put a header at the top of the file like so:  <figure class="highlight plain"><table><tr><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">---</span><br><span class="line">date: 2018-05-04 16:48:00</span><br><span class="line">---</span><br><span class="line">Markdown for page starts here</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure></p><p>  then the generated website will preserve the date of the original post even  if the file is later changed.+ To add a static page to the introductory (<em>Learn more</em>) or developer (<em>Develop</em>)  sections, you will need to  + Add a new file to the <code>doc/content/learn-more</code> or <code>doc/content/develop</code> directories.  + Add an entries to the <code>doc/tpl/__en__</code> and <code>doc/tpl/__sidebar__</code> files that    map the filename to a title to show in the sidebar links of the website.+ To add a new section to the links at the top of the website (a sibling to the  <em>Learn more</em> and <em>Develop</em> links), you’ll need to do the above <em>plus</em> add an entry  to the <code>doc/data/menu.yml</code> file.</p><p>For more information about formatting files, see the<a href="https://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Markdown</a> and<a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hexo</a> documentation.Markdown is the format we use for pages while Hexo is thejavascript package that kw-doc uses to process the markdowncontent into HTML.</p><h2 id="Description-of-documentation-files"><a href="#Description-of-documentation-files" class="headerlink" title="Description of documentation files"></a>Description of documentation files</h2><ul><li><code>package.json</code> and <code>package-lock.json</code> are files that specify which javascript packagesare needed to generate and publish the documentation.</li><li><code>doc/config.js</code> is javascript declaring website-wide configuration.</li><li><code>doc/data/menu.yml</code> declares links at the top of each web page on the site.</li><li><code>doc/tpl/__sidebar__</code> organizes the sidebar links for static sections of the website.</li><li><code>doc/tpl/__en__</code> maps filenames and sidebar names into different languages/locales.</li><li><code>doc/content/index.jade</code> is a template used to construct the front page of the website.</li></ul>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;In order to make the SENSEI website more dynamic, we will start using github pages to host the website.
The website is generated from fil
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hexo</title>
    <link href="https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2016/04/28/kw-doc/"/>
    <id>https://kitware.github.io/sensei/2016/04/28/kw-doc/</id>
    <published>2016-04-29T00:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-05-09T20:41:02.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thanks for using kw-doc which is based on Hexo and its template from its own documentation.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;Thanks for using kw-doc which is based on Hexo and its template from its own documentation.&lt;/p&gt;

      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
